documentforce.com 2010-02-13

# Salesforce.com Privacy Statement - salesforce.com

We [self-certify](http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list) compliance with  

## Salesforce.com Privacy Notice – Full Privacy Statement Highlights

### Information Collected

  * When you request additional information or register for services, the Company will ask you to provide basic contact information.
  * When you purchase services online, the Company will ask you to provide billing information.
  * Salesforce.com uses common Internet technologies, such as cookies and Web beacons, to keep track of interactions with the Company's Web sites and emails.
  * For more information about salesforce.com’s information collection practices, please click here .

### Important Information

  * Salesforce.com’s full Privacy Statement contains more information about the Company’s information practices.
  * Salesforce.com is a certified licensee of the [TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?companyName=Salesforce.com,%20Inc.&sealid=102). The Company is also a certified licensee of the [TRUSTe EU Safe Harbor Seal](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.salesforce.com&sealid=102&lang=en) and abides by the [EU Safe Harbor Framework](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

### Use of Information

  * Salesforce.com uses information collected to provide you with the services you request.
  * Salesforce.com may use information collected to provide you with additional information about the Company’s services, partners, promotions, and events.
  * Salesforce.com may use information collected to improve the Company’s Web sites and services.
  * Salesforce.com does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. Salesforce.com may share information collected with other companies that work on Salesforce.com’s behalf.
  * For more information about salesforce.com’s use of information collected, please click here.

### Customer Data

  * Customers of salesforce.com use the Company’s services to host data and information (“Customer Data”).
  * Salesforce.com will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the salesforce.com Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records of Customer Data may be viewed or accessed only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the salesforce.com Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law.

### Communications Preferences

  * Every marketing email from salesforce.com contains instructions on how to opt out of receiving further marketing emails from the Company.
  * If you provide salesforce.com with contact information, you may choose how the Company uses your information by clicking [here](http://www.salesforce.com/profile).
  * For more information about managing communications you receive from salesforce.com and instructions for updating information provided when registering for the Company’s services, please click here.

### How to Contact Us

For more information about salesforce.com’s information practices, please view the Company’s full Privacy Statement. Questions regarding salesforce.com’s Privacy Statement or information practices should be directed here or by mail:

Salesforce.com Privacy   
The Landmark @ One Market Street, Suite 300   
San Francisco, CA 94105

If salesforce.com does not adequately respond, please click here to contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with salesforce.com.
